Writing functions, understanding scope, handling errors (try/except), and organizing code into modules
Learned to work in venv environment using VScode 
			  press ctr+shift+p
			  select interpreter in venv 
Learned to do simple projects by organizing code in modules like 
		     1. Simple calculator with history 
			     folder goes like : Simple_cal/main.py calcularor/init, operations, history/ readme etc 
			2. Simple number guessing game 