Flask is a Python web framework. 
That means it helps you: Build web apps, Build REST APIs,
Handle HTTP requests (like when a browser or another program sends data or asks for data)
Flask is lightweight and beginner-friendly. It's like learning how to speak to the internet in Python.
A REST API is how two systems talk over the web.		
A Flask REST API lets you create your own service that can receive, store, and respond with data.

What is a Route?
 a path or door in your web app.

When someone visits http://127.0.0.1:5000/hello, you decide what happens — that’s a route.

example:
from flask import Flask

app = Flask(__name__)

@app.route('/hello')
def say_hello():
    return "Hello, world!"
if you go to http://127.0.0.1:5000/hello, it shows: Hello world

What is a GET request?
A GET request is like asking for information.

@app.route('/get-ip')
def get_ip():
    return {"ip": "192.168.1.1"}

What is a POST request?

A POST request is like sending data to the server.


from flask import request

@app.route('/send-ip', methods=['POST'])
def receive_ip():
    data = request.json  # Get JSON data from request
    ip = data.get('ip')
    return {"message": f"You sent IP: {ip}"}

How to return JSON?
JSON = a special format computers use to share data, like:
{"name": "Alice", "score": 85}

ex:
from flask import jsonify

@app.route('/json')
def send_json():
    return jsonify({"status": "ok", "result": 42})


Summary:
Use API's to get data
Use POST to send data 
